feedzilla.com 2006-12-06

# Privacy policy

## FeedZilla Privacy Policy 

Last updated: November 11, 2005 

Protecting your privacy and securing your personal information are our top concerns. We will never sell, exchange or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties without first obtaining your express consent. 

The Privacy Policy covers the site [www.FeedZilla.com ](http://www.stepnewz.com/) (the "Site") and forms part of the User Agreement. The Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use your personal information. If you do not agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access our services. This Agreement is effective upon acceptance in registration for new members, and is otherwise effective on November 11, 2005 for all users.  

**1.   A Special Note About Children **

The FeedZilla Service and Site are not intended for and may not be used by children (persons under the age of 18). 

**2.   Information We Collect **

When using FeedZilla, you remain the sole owner of the information you provide us with. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. 

2.1. Account Information. When you choose to use our services, We collect the following contact information ("Your Account Information"): first name, last name, email address, country, URL of your website or weblog, username and password to identify you and send notifications related to the use of the service. 

2.2. Billing Information. When you subscribe to any of our fee-based services, We collect the following billing information (“Your Billing Information”): first name, last name, company name (only for companies), address and country. Coldbrook does not collect credit card information. We use PayPal ( [www.paypal.com ](http://www.paypal.com/)), a third party online payment provider to accept and process payments. When you pay with PayPal, your credit card and bank numbers are never seen by Coldbrook. Your financial information stays safe. Visit PayPal.com to learn more about PayPal privacy, prevention and protection. 

2.2. Additional Information. We automatically track, collect and aggregate certain information based upon your behavior on the Site. This information may include, but is not limited to, browser types, IP addresses, referring sites, pages visited, number of visitors, content selected and viewed and services purchased. This information cannot be used to personally identify you. This means that your session will be tracked, but you will be anonymous. We may also collect personal correspondence you send us or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on the Site. 

2.3. Cookies. Like most web sites, FeedZilla uses a standard technology called cookies. A cookie is a tiny piece of data stored on the member's hard drive tied to information about the member. We use ID session cookies to manage session on FeedZilla. Once members close the browser, the cookie expires. Cookies can also enable FeedZilla to personalize your experience when you are signed in to the Site and improve our internal business processes. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our services. We do not use cookies to collect personal information from any member. 

2.4. Anonymous visitors. You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. 

**3.   How We Use Your Personal Information **

3.1. Personal Information. We use your personal information to facilitate and improve the service you request. We use your personal information to contact you; maintain a safe environment; collect fees; improve marketing strategy, analyze site usage, and improve and customize our Site. 

3.2. Communication. FeedZilla will communicate with you through emails and announcements posted on the Site. FeedZilla will always send out non-promotional and service-related information. This information may relate to the proper functioning of your account, changes to the Privacy Policy and/or User Agreement and also planned service suspensions and outages. FeedZilla sends all its members a welcoming email to verify if their email address is correct. When you register to become a member you choose whether you want to receive FeedZilla newsletters. 

3.3. Customization and safety. Additionally, we may use Your Information to provide you with personalized content, instructions and services; to provide you with information about our services, news and events through the Site or email; to understand on an aggregated basis how our services are used, to analyze site usage and determine what types of content and services are most popular; to secure your experience on the site. 

**4.   With Whom We May Share Your Personal Information **

Protecting your privacy is our top concern. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy and our User Agreement, we will never sell, exchange or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties without first obtaining your express consent. 

4.1. Legal request. We may disclose any of your information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, legal process served on FeedZilla or to maintain trust and safety in the Site and exercise FeedZilla' User Agreement or legal rights. 

4.2. Third parties intermediaries. We may disclose profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties to provide specific services. The information we disclose cannot be used to personally identify you. 

4.3. FeedZilla community. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily post material in publicly accessible areas of FeedZilla, this constitutes public and not private communications and may be accessed, collected and used by others. 

4.4. Other corporate entities. Y our personal information will not be shared outside our company. In case we merge with or are acquired by another business entity, Coldbrook may share your information with that business entity. Should such a combination occur, you will retain ownership rights to Your Information and the ability to delete Your Information at any time. Additionally, if your information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice. 

4.5. Third party Web sites. The Site contains links to third party sites that provide external services or that advertise or link on our Site. We do not share Your Information with third party Web sites you can access from FeedZilla. Coldbrook does not control the collection or use of information by these companies. You should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services. 

4.6. Partners. Coldbrook may partner with affiliates in order to provide our services to their users. If you sign up with FeedZilla through one of these affiliates, Your Information may be shared between that affiliate and Coldbrook. These partners are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of your information for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific provision of our services to you, unless you have explicitly given your prior permission to them for additional uses. 

**5.   How You Can Access, Review and Change Your Personal Information **

5.1. Accessing/Updating Information. You can review Your Information and make any changes to this information, at any time by logging into your account on the Site. However, you may not update or delete the information you post in publicly accessible areas of the Site. 

5.2. Account Deactivation. Upon your request, we will deactivate your account and information from our databases. To make this request, email [privacy@FeedZilla.com ](mailto:privacy@FeedZilla.com). Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity. However, some personal information may need to be maintained if it is connected with billing information or as required by law. 

**6.   Security procedures **

All Your Information is stored on Coldbrook' secure server at Brinkster, our web hosting company located in the United States . Your FeedZilla account is protected by an encrypted password. We recommend you do not disclose your password to anyone. Our network and server are secure with firewall system, 24/7 monitoring, break-in detection technologies and physical security. Only selected Coldbrook personnel have access to customer information via password. Our employees and data processors are obliged to respect the confidentiality of Your Information. 

**7.   Changes in Our Privacy Policy **

We may amend our Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Site ( [www.FeedZilla.com ](http://www.feedzilla.com/)). All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. This agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a writing signed by you and Coldbrook Business Corp. 

**8.   How to contact us **

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@FeedZilla.com ](mailto:privacy@FeedZilla.com).
